紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   咖喱味的虛寒
翻譯   吃冰棒
翻譯   WalkingNerd
翻譯   持久
翻譯   蘇小黛
翻譯   somehacker
翻譯   肉松
時間軸   Ans
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第二集
總統頒布邊境限制令
康威競選團隊對總統言論的回應
康威
戰爭英雄
艾·麥卡倫急事  需要和他談談
托馬斯·耶茨
安德伍德夫婦的"傳聲筒"
艾·麥卡倫我在這里給你留了禮物
20分鐘有效  萬圣節快樂
連接穩定
您確定要徹底刪除選定文件嗎
文件刪除中
琥珀警報
僵尸出動了  去墓地看看
委員會將就安德伍德的
宣戰請求舉辦聽證會
文件刪除中
任務完成
艾·麥卡倫我能發修復方案了嗎
發送失敗
發送成功
艾·麥卡倫
我能發修復方案了嗎
我們得立刻行動  不然會出事
這是你的坑  去填吧
無信號
我要求國會
I demand that this Congress
正式對哈里發國宣戰
declare a formal declaration of war against ICO,
在本土  也在海外
both here and abroad.
確保處理宣戰的委員會
Make sure the committee dealing with the declaration of war
不會進入表決
never gets to a vote.
我們得回到總統罪行的問題上
We need to get back to the president's crimes.
那才是新聞
That's the story.
讓他們談什么都好  就是別談那篇文章
Get them talking about anything but that goddamn article.
我們得加大恐懼感
We need to dial up the terror.
戰爭婊子
War whore!
我們如果想平安度過
The only way that we are gonna survive this...
就得讓他們贏
is if they win.
幫他們贏
Help them win.
你桑蒂諾的朋友  蒂姆·科貝特打來了
Your friend from The Sentinel called, Tim Corbet.
你什么時候來科羅拉多州又有時間
You're ever in Colorado with some time on your hands...
還剩兩周  很難反對戰爭
We're two weeks out. It's hard to say no to war.
他們要利用宣戰的事做調查
They're gonna use the Declaration of War to investigate.
是的
That's right.
他們要用弗蘭克要求組建的委員會調查他
They're gonna use the committee Frank asked for to investigate him.
-該死  -是啊  道格
- Fuck. - That's right, Doug.
"該死"
"Fuck."
你怎么老玩那個
Why do you keep playing with that?
因為我疑心重啊
Because I'm skeptical.
你覺得這個真管用嗎
Do you think this really works?
是為了讓候選人看起來眼熟
Oh, it's just about making the candidate seem familiar,
讓選民在他臉上看見自己的影子
so that the voter sees herself in him.
但你調得有點過了
But... you've gone too far.
好了
There.
恭喜你  弗蘭西斯  我投你一票
Congratulations, Francis. You have my vote.
-你什么時候去紐約  -現在就走
- When do you leave for New York? - Now.
然后再回來和凱茜一起出席活動
Then I'm back for the event with Cathy.
麥卡倫做的事真的很危險
It's very risky, what Macallan is doing.
你覺得值得嗎
Do you think it's worth it?
-丹頓和夏普剛請了律師  -他們不想作證
- Danton and Sharp just lawyered up. - They don't want to testify?
不可能在大選之前
And there's no way subpoenas get them
傳召他們去委員會作證了
in front of the committee before the election.
有傳言說委員會
There's a rumor the committee's
想和加勒特·沃克做交易
trying to make a deal with Garrett Walker.
不  沃克不想傷害黨的選情
No, Walker doesn't want to do damage to the party.
那吉姆·馬修斯為什么同意出席
So why did Jim Matthews agree to appear?
已經有記者拿這事砸我了
I'm already getting pummeled with questions about it.
他有什么可說的嗎
Does he have anything to say?
就算他保持沉默
Uh, even if he pleads the Fifth,
也是能給總統抹黑的
they get a perp walk that implicates the president.
我就沒見過有誰吃那東西
I didn't know anyone actually ate those.
我饞了一整年了
I look forward to this stuff all year.
委員會成員有什么料在我們手上嗎
Do we have anything on the committee members?
恐怕眼下還沒什么猛料
Nothing too juicy yet, I'm afraid.
副主席干了一個年輕男職員
Vice chairman had an affair with a young male staffer
然后向他老婆出柜  老新聞了
before he came out to his wife. Old news.
委員會主席干凈得很
Committee chairman's squeaky clean
只有點退稅之類的小問題
other than a minor back-tax issue.
把手中掌握的他人的裸體照片
或性愛視頻放到網上
多半是分道揚鑣的前伴侶所為
我倒是找到了段主席幕僚長的色情報復視頻
I did find some revenge porn on the chairman's chief of staff,
不過我覺得沒什么價值
but I don't think it's worth much.
能嚇住她嗎
Is it enough to scare her?
也就讓她丟丟人吧  再多就不太可能了
Embarrass her, probably. More than that, probably not.
我得說面具您戴著好看多了  安德伍德夫人
I gotta say, they look a lot better on you, Mrs. Underwood,
要比康威州長戴著好看
than they would on Governor Conway.
也許這就是他不想掏錢的原因
Maybe that's why he didn't wanna pay for it.
面具將分發給大紐約交通運輸管理局的工程師
These masks will be distributed to all MTA engineers,
售票員和維護工人
conductors and maintenance workers.
這一款應對化武襲擊非常有效
And this model is highly effective in case of a chemical attack.
我想阿德拉迪市長有幾句話要講
And I believe Mayor Adalardi would like to say a few words.
好的
Absolutely.
確保公共運輸部門的安保措施全覆蓋
Safety in all branches of the public transportation system
-是我的首要考慮  -肯
- is my number one priority. - Ken?
-其中包括地鐵  公交  -沒事  我認識他
- That means subways, that means buses... - It's fine, I know him.
你怎么來了
What are you doing here?
我就在這站下啊
What? This is my stop.
-你氣色不錯  -還行吧
- Well, you look well. - Well, I can't complain.
就那樣唄  只是
Can't complain, except...
我想你知道蒂姆的事吧
Well, I'm sure you heard about Tim.
科貝特  不清楚
Corbet? No.
-貝絲沒打電話嗎  -沒有啊
- Beth didn't call? - No.
老天  我真不希望你從我這里聽說這事
Oh, man. I hate to be the one to tell you this.
蒂姆去阿肯色河游玩
Tim went out on the Arkansas River.
他已經失蹤兩天了
He's been missing for two days now.
我還以為總統肯定知道呢
I thought for sure the President would have heard.
我都無法想象弗蘭克會多難受
I mean, I can't imagine how Frank's gonna take this.
我的天啊  貝絲和孩子們肯定傷心死了
Oh, my goodness! Beth and the kids must be so distraught.
當然  可是弗蘭克和蒂姆的關系不一般
Sure. But Frank and Tim's relationship was special.
很高興見到你  克萊爾
It's great to see you, Claire.
你能讓弗蘭克給我打個電話嗎
Would you ask Frank to give me a call?
-安德伍德夫人  -請稍等
- Mrs. Underwood? - Uh, just one moment.
看見剛才和我說話的那位先生了嗎
See that gentleman I was speaking to?
去請他等我一下  謝謝
Go ask him to wait for me, please.
各位州長  我們時間不多了
Governors, we are running out of time.
你們各位
The fact that you are here
大老遠來參加這場緊急會議
at this emergency meeting on such short notice
就已經讓美國人民知道
tells the American people that
你們和我一樣  擔憂他們的安全
you are as concerned about their safety as I am.
恐懼是不可接受的
Terror is unacceptable.
我拒絕接受
I do not accept it.
但我們不能被
But we will not be deterred
華盛頓的處理不力拖后腿
by Washington's failure to address it.
我們要勠力合作  肩并肩  共進退
We will work together, side by side, fighting back.
在每個州  每座城市  每個街區展開反擊
State by state, city by city, neighborhood by neighborhood.
因為各位不要掉以輕心
Because, make no mistake...
我們在打一場影響整個時代的戰爭
we are engaged in the battle of our time.
作為美國人意味著什么
The question of what it is to be an American,
美國性的核心本質
the very essence of American-ness,
我們選擇的開放自由的生活
how we choose to lead our lives, open and free,
這些都受到了威脅
is on the line.
恐懼是非美國的
Fear is un-American.
沒錯  偏偏在萬圣節這天對各位說這番話
And yes, the irony of saying those words to you on Halloween,
這諷刺性我也意識到了
of all days, is not lost on me.
但雖然我們作為美國人
But although we may choose, as Americans,
可能會為了取樂  每年主動嚇自己一次
to scare ourselves once a year for fun...
除了這一天之外  誰也不能
no one else tells any American
告訴美國人什么時候該嚇得發抖
when to shake in their boots at any other time.
我要下達一項行政命令
So I am issuing an executive order,
憑借我
by virtue of the authority vested in me
作為美國總統
as President of the United States
和三軍統帥的的權力
and commander in chief of the armed forces.
憑借憲法和我國的法律
By our Constitution and the laws of our land,
包括什么什么法第多少多少章
including Section Blah-Blah of the Blah-Blah Act
還有某某法令第多少多少章
and Section Blah-Blah of Title Blah-Blah,
第哪條狗屁款
Paragraph Bullshit-Bullshit.
以防你不明白這是怎么回事
In case you have no idea what's going on,
我要擴充這些州的國民警衛隊
I'm swelling these states' National Guard troops
以確保選舉日公共場合的安全性
to create secure public spaces on Election Day.
我督促這些州長合并投票站
I'm urging these governors to consolidate their polling sites
建立"投票中心"
and create quote, unquote "voting centers"
讓民眾覺得出門投票是安全的
so that people feel safe to come out and vote.
我贊揚偉大的亞利桑那州的州長
I'm commending Governor Sally Morrison
薩莉·莫里森
of the great state of Arizona,
因為她在最近的初選中為我們樹立了
for giving us all such a good example of voting centers
投票中心的好榜樣
as used in their recent primary.
但我其實是在
But what I'm really doing
引誘五個關鍵州的州長
is seducing the governors of five key states.
新澤西  內華達  伊利諾伊
New Jersey, Nevada, Illinois,
俄亥俄和賓州
Ohio and Pennsylvania.
州長分別是哈克特  努涅茲  加里納德
Messrs. Harcourt, Nuñez, Gallinard,
奧姆斯泰德  還有馬修斯
Olmstead and Matthews.
你們還記得馬修斯吧
You remember Matthews, don't you?
加勒特·沃克總統的前副總統
Former vice president to President Garrett Walker.
就是個眼光狹隘的偷筆毛賊
Nothing but a provincial and petty pen-stealer.
但我需要他
But I need him.
想贏得這次選舉  我需要他們五個都支持我
I need all five on my side if I'm gonna win this election.
從以往來看  馬修是我們已知的最大未知數
Matthews, in our history, he's the biggest known unknown.
我差點忘了  金童也來了
And I almost forgot. The boy wonder is here.
我不容小覷的對手
My worthy opponent.
他坐立不安  我卻如魚得水
Out of his element and stuck in mine.
但你看  在政治中聲望[身高]決定一切
But, you see, in politics, stature is everything.
你也能看出來
And wouldn't you say that
小威·康越來越矮了[底氣不足]Willy C is getting shorter by the minute?
總統提出的這些邊境限制令
These border restrictions the president is proposing...
軍隊是否該執行它們  將軍
should the military play a role in enforcing them, General?
我們應該退后一步
I think we need to take a step back
站在大局看國家安全的當務之急
and look at our national security priorities.
以及如何調動軍隊
And what constitutes appropriate deployment
才是合理合法的
of our serving men and women.
我們是退役軍人
As veterans,
此事讓康威州長和我尤其掛心
this issue is a personal one for Governor Conway and me.
-你和  -我再跟你說
- Would you and-- - I'll tell you something else.
州長不會親口這么說
You won't hear this from the governor himself,
但在他的軍旅生涯中
but his military career
非凡的勇敢行為不計其數
is distinguished by exceptional acts of bravery.
尤其是  讓他獲得
In particular, the incident for which
紫心勛章的那次行動  格外突出
he was awarded the Purple Heart stands out.
這表明了他能成為怎樣的三軍統帥
Speaks to the kind of commander in chief he will be.
也證明了在我看來  是無畏的智慧
Demonstrates what I call fearless wisdom.
美國應該盡早聽聽他立功的來龍去脈
Someday soon, America needs to hear the full story of that day.
感謝您的參與  布洛哈特將軍
Thank you for your time, General Brockhart.
很高興接受采訪
Glad to talk to you.
接下的《特別報道》  我們將關注
Coming up next on Special Report, we take a look at...
我對天發誓  要是安德伍德往邊境派兵
I swear to God, if Underwood puts soldiers on those borders,
我第一個站出來讓軍人抗命
I'll be the first to tell them not to listen.
在撥款分配方面
In terms of allocation of funds,
水源問題讓我整夜發愁
it's our water supply that keeps me up at night.
羅杰  你是說保護基礎設施嗎
Roger, are you talking about protecting the infrastructure?
基礎設施還有水源問題
Infrastructure and water sources.
水庫  水壩  還有輸水管道系統
Reservoirs, the dams, the tunnel delivery systems--
所有這些  是的
All of it, yes.
保護它們免遭恐襲  當然
Protection from terrorism, sure,
但選民們還看到了更大的危險
but the voters see even greater dangers.
建設性的  環境方面的  藻類毒素
Structural, environmental, toxins from algae.
水藻是我們的大麻煩
Algae's quite a problem for us.
關鍵問題是  聯邦政府盡力了嗎
The big question here, are the feds doing all they can do?
聯邦政府還想做更多事情
Well, the feds want to do even more.
那就是我們今天聚在這里的原因
That's the reason that we're all meeting here today.
先生們  我現在看到的
Now, look, gentlemen, all I can see
是我們大家都在爭吵
is that we're in violent agreement with each other.
羅杰  我們認識多久了
I mean, Roger, how long have we known each other?
多長時間了
How far do we go back?
我還有頭發的時候你就認識我了  總統先生
You knew me when I had hair, Mr. President.
但不管怎樣  我的選民都說
It doesn't change the fact that my constituents are saying,
"我們需要的是橋  不是戰區"
"Give me a bridge, not a war zone."
我的意思是
All I'm saying is that
我們要及時預測并扼制威脅
we need to anticipate threats when we can and thwart them.
我的意思是  大選將至
I'm saying that we're days away from an election,
我不想把事情搞砸
and I don't wanna upset the apple cart.
抱歉我離開一下
Excuse me for just a moment.
威爾  你看到這個了嗎
Will, have you seen this?
好  我回頭找他
All right. I'll deal with him later.
告訴我她具體說了什么
Tell me exactly what she said.
只說她是從肯·卡斯維爾那里聽到的
Just that she heard it from Ken Caswell.
我向薩里達當局核實過了  先生
I checked with the local authorities in Salida, sir.
不太妙
It doesn't look good.
-可能性  -加強搜索力度
- The chances of-- - Amp up the search.
無論他們是需要物資還是人手
Whatever materials and personnel they need
除了他們已經有的  都給他們
in addition to what they have, give them.
再聯系一下貝絲·科貝特  我想和她通話
And reach out to Beth Corbet. I'd like to speak to her directly.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
從2012年起我就沒睡過一個好覺
I haven't slept a good night's sleep since 2012.
但我覺得當選官員不睡覺的話
But I guess elected officials don't sleep
我們的選民就能睡好了
so our constituents can.
成功打擊恐怖活動的證據
The proof of success in fighting terror...
就是民眾對此毫不知曉
is something the public never hears about.
我州的一座城市
A certain city in my state
是國內最大的恐襲目標
wears the biggest target in the nation.
紐約州和紐約市
The city and state of New York...
十五年來默默地勝利著
has scored silent wins for 15 years...
從未宣戰
without a declaration of war.
好吧
Now...
大多數時候
in most cases...
我會說各州可以進行自我管理
I would argue the states can take care of themselves.
總統先生
Mr. President!
沒事  繼續  州長
Well, by all means, continue, Governor.
你之前在說什么  失眠
What... what was that part you were talking about? Insomnia?
我的意思是
My point is,
在座各位都是美國人  我們都愛這個國家
we're all Americans in this room, and we all love this country.
我想感謝總統
and I'd like to thank the president
給我機會討論這一非常重要的話題
for the opportunity to discuss this very important topic,
我很抱歉  我的時間太緊張
and apologize for, uh, being on such a tight schedule.
我們非常感謝
Well, we are enormously grateful
今天州長能抽出時間趕來參加
that the governor took the time to come and join us today.
我只是想弄明白
I'm just trying to understand.
克萊爾  如果我的話冒犯到了你
Claire, if I said anything to offend you,
那完全是
it was entirely...
你懂我的  我說話不動腦子
I mean, you know me. No filter.
那就是讓我擔心的事
And that's what worries me.
我只是憑直覺行事  肯
I'm just operating on instinct, Ken.
你來這兒是有什么目的嗎
Did you come down here with an agenda?
沒有  我...
No. I mean...
我一直想找弗蘭克  但今天只是...
I have been trying to reach Frank, but today was just...
我看到你要出席一場活動
I saw that you were appearing at an event
就來打個招呼
and I showed up to say hi.
我真的在這附近工作
I... I really do work around here,
在一條叫"華爾"的街上  知道嗎
on a street called "Wall", you know?
但你提到了
But then you made reference
兩個非常親密的朋友的事
to something about two very close friends
這不關任何人的事  包括你
that's nobody's business, including yours.
你自己也這么說
And you even said so yourself,
肯  你是個大嘴巴
Ken, that you have an awfully big mouth.
我
I...
我失去了一位好友
I lost a dear friend.
我愛蒂姆  大家都愛他
I loved Tim. Everybody did.
你還特別暗指了弗蘭西斯
And you implied Francis especially.
是的  我是說  那完全是另一回事
Well, yeah. I mean... That was a whole other thing.
怎么是另一回事
In what way?
就是...你想讓我說什么
In... What do you want me to say?
我相信我知道的并不比你多
I'm sure I don't know anything you don't.
我只是很想知道你是怎么想的
I'm just very interested in your perspective.
弗蘭克很敬重蒂姆  他愿為他做任何事
Frank worshipped Tim, would have done anything for him.
我說不好
I don't know.
如果當時的世道是另一番樣子  誰知道呢
If the world were a different place back then... who knows?
那是很久之前的事了  后來他遇見了你
That was a long time ago. And then he met you.
他真有福氣
And lucky him.
瞧  要說我的公司
Look, in terms of my firm and...
和我聯系總統那么費勁...
and trying to get the president's ear...
這的確有點尷尬
I mean, yeah, it's a little embarrassing
跟我有30多年交情的老朋友
that my friend of 30-whatever years
沒有時間接我的電話
didn't have time to pick up the phone.
他應該回你電話的
He should have called you back.
弗蘭西斯和蒂姆是非常要好的朋友
Francis and Tim were very good friends.
但是  肯  隨著年齡的增長
But, you know, Ken, the older I get,
我發現妄下判斷是很危險的
I learn that assumptions are dangerous.
是啊  好吧
Sure. Okay.
很高興見到你
It was great to see you.
她在哪
So where is she?
計劃有變  她需要留在紐約
Change of plans. She needed to stay in New York.
她要我為這次會議做了準備的
She asked me to put something together for this.
是嗎  臨時有事
Yeah? Well, something came up.
副總統會替她出席
The vice president will be filling in for her.
我的天...
Oh, my...
你好啊
Hey, man.
我們以前組過一個很糟糕的樂隊
Uh, we played in a terrible band together back in the day.
我們那時還年少  不需要付贍養費
Before adulthood and alimony came crashing down.
兩個前妻嗎
Two exes?
第一夫人在哪
So, uh, where's the First Lady?
臨時有事
Something came up.
我想問你幾個關于為競選工作的問題
I'd love to ask you a few questions about working on the campaign.
我只是個講稿撰寫人
I'm just a speechwriter.
是啊  你怎么得到這份工作的
Exactly. How the hell did that happen?
歡迎來到對外關系委員會
Welcome to the Council on Foreign Relations
此次特別活動  跨越國境:前進的道路
and this special event on Crossing Borders: The Way Forward.
這好像是個搖擺州派對
I smell a swing state party.
注意語氣  瑞克
Tone, Rick.
你不必大費周章召集數十位州長
You didn't have to round up dozens of governors
只為跟我們五個談話
just to talk to the five of us.
你們來這里是因為我們在擔心
You're here because there have been concerning threats
你們各州的遠郊郡存在威脅
in exurban counties in each of your states.
你能再說具體一點嗎
Could you be more specific?
我們在關注亨特頓  埃爾科  杰弗遜郡
We're keeping an eye on Hunterdon, Elko, Jefferson counties.
還有切斯特和麥克亨利
Also Chester and McHenry.
所以在大選來臨前
Which is why it's crucial
我們必須要與你們各州的
that we work with your states' administrations
州政府合作
leading up to the election.
這些選區
Every one of those precincts
都是典型的共和黨票倉
is a typically Republican stronghold.
這和黨派關系無關
This isn't about party affiliation.
如總統所說  這事關國家安全
As the president said, this is about security.
我們相信這些舉措
Now, we believe this course of action,
對投票站增加警力
the voting centers with the added law enforcement,
能充分保證
will give us everything that we need
選舉的安全性
to protect the integrity of the ballot box.
好吧  但我代表
Okay, but speaking for
奧姆斯泰德州長  也許還有所有我們的上司
Governor Olmstead and maybe all of our bosses,
想問問  我們怎么知道這些措施
how can we be sure that these measures
不會讓選民不敢去投票
won't discourage everyone from getting to the polls?
-比如  民主黨人  -我們必須冒這個險
- I.E., Democrats. - It's a chance we have to take.
但我們認為不會出現這樣的結果
But we don't believe it'll play out that way.
我們俄亥俄州的選票非常接近
We're in an extremely close race in Ohio.
重要的是預防可能的
Preventing further acts of terrorism
恐怖襲擊  塔妮婭
is just about all that matters, Tanya.
我非常清楚  威脅的增加
Now, I do realize with these heightened threats
給了你們的州長額外的壓力
comes an additional strain on the governors of your states.
所以...
So...
我要對你們所有人說...
I say to each and every one of you...
告訴我們該如何幫助你們
tell me how we can help.
拋開確實存在的道德問題不談
Putting aside the very real moral questions,
封鎖邊境怎么能可行
how is shutting down the borders even feasible?
我知道這項政策會損害部分人的利益
I know this policy is going to hurt some people,
但容我解釋一下為什么必須這樣做
but let me explain why it's necessary.
副總統隨時可以補充
And the vice president should feel free to jump in.
好玩嗎
But is it fun?
為安德伍德找話說
Putting words in the Underwoods' mouths?
我的工作不是這樣的
That's not what I do.
恰好相反
It's more like the opposite.
我只是盡量表達出...
I just try and articulate...
他們的想法和心聲
what's on their minds and in their hearts.
你是這么看待你的工作的
That's how you see your job?
基本上  我的工作就是當個隱形人
Basically, my job is to remain invisible.
那晚上你和他們在一起嗎
Were you with them that night?
吉姆·米勒被殺的那晚
The night Jim Miller was killed?
這我不能回答
I'm not gonna answer that.
那就當作默認
I'll take that as a "yes."
別這樣
Don't.
我只是想了解你的工作
I'm just trying to understand what you do.
那你就弄錯重點了
Then you're missing the point.
我不是主角  史蒂夫  我不是
I'm not the story, Steve. I'm just not.
你把自己說得可有可無
You make yourself sound replaceable.
事實如此
I am.
-我為總統效勞  -還有第一夫人
- I serve at the pleasure of the president. - And the First Lady?
民主黨副總統候選人
The Democratic vice presidential candidate...
沒錯  還有她
Yeah. Her, too.
但你為他們倆撰寫講稿
But you write speeches for both of them?
更多是為安德伍德夫人寫
Most often for Mrs. Underwood.
將她的想法和心聲表達出來
Articulating what's on her mind and in her heart?
我只是個傳聲筒
I'm just a mouthpiece.
她有交給你其他"任務"嗎
Has she put you in charge of any other parts?
你還是那么混賬
You're still an asshole, man.
祝你贍養費的事好運
Good luck with the alimony.
-真夠嗆  -還算順利吧
- That was rough. - It went fine.
這維系不下去的
It's not sustainable.
你的看法是什么
I mean, what do you think?
-什么的看法  -總統急于宣戰之舉
- About what? - About the president's rush to war.
華府至少有一半人都認為這太過分了
At least half the Beltway seems to think it's outrageous.
是很過分
It is outrageous.
我們可以辭職以表示抗議
We could resign our posts, you know, in protest.
我相信我們能說服其他內閣成員一起辭職
I bet we can convince others of the cabinet to do the same thing.
我是想說  目的就是要過分
Outrageous by design, I was going to say.
總統的做法很聰明
It's smart, what the president's doing.
-為他的民調加了分  -唐納德
- It's serving him in the polls. - Donald.
我們先...退幾步說話
Let's... take a step back for a moment.
我低估了你  真的
I underestimated you. I did.
你當代總統時  我對你信心不足
When you were acting president, my faith was less than full.
但現在我能理解你當時的困境和壓力...
But now, I understand the terrible box you were in, the forces--
凱茜  我得...打斷你
Cathy, I'm gonna... I'm gonna stop you.
我真的不知道你在說些什么
I honestly don't know what you're talking about.
你是說你的計劃是要
Are you telling me your plan
裝作若無其事直到1月20日總統就職嗎
is just to phone it in until January 20th?
唐納德  你是怎么回事
Come on, Donald. What's happened to you?
想當初
Back in the day,
你和瑪喬莉總是站在
you and Marjorie were at
所有進步革新的最前線
the forefront of every progressive cause,
真正地為善而戰
literally fighting the good fight.
這些人
These people...
我們真要讓他們這么做嗎
Can we really let them do this?
你想緬懷往事  凱茜  好吧
You wanna walk down memory lane, Cathy? Okay.
記得黨代會嗎  記得政治新聞網那篇文章嗎
Remember the convention? Remember the Politico article?
我給了你一條退路
I offered you an out.
你當時就該把握機會下臺
You should've taken that opportunity to resign, then and there.
-當時的情況和現在不同  -沒兩樣
- Circumstances were nothing like this. - Sure they were.
你當時只是不愿認清事實
You just didn't want to see it.
再告訴你一件事
And, just so you know,
在她完全失智前  瑪喬莉就說準了
right before her mind was truly gone, Marjorie called it.
她看出了你和弗蘭克·安德伍德的私下結盟
She saw the unholy alliance you were making with Frank Underwood.
她早就說準了
She called it.
今天我們倆上司的會面...
So this meeting between our bosses today...
總統期待
The president is looking forward to
與馬修斯州長展開有成效的會談
a productive discussion with Governor Matthews.
這里只有我們倆  咱就別說廢話了
There's no one else here. Can we cut the crap?
你要我們刻意壓制投票
You want us to engage in voter suppression.
我不會用那樣的字眼
It's not a phrase I'd ever use.
隨便你  那就稱之為"降低動力"吧
Fine. Call it "motor depression" for all I care.
我們懂的  白人是問題所在
We get it. White people are the problem.
是共和黨人  我懂
Republicans. Understood.
但我的上司并不參加再選
But my boss doesn't happen to be up for reelection.
我洗耳恭聽
I'm listening.
我就說三個字  "熔渣堆"
I have two words for you. "Slag heap."
馬修斯希望環保署把費城郊區
Matthews wants the EPA to name a slag heap
一座熔渣堆列為特別清污地點
on the outskirts of Philadelphia as a Superfund site.
我高度懷疑這在大選前能實現
I seriously doubt that can happen before the election.
你該克服自我懷疑  道格
I think you should battle your doubts, Doug.
州長愿意讓過去成為往事
The governor is willing to let the past stay in the past.
但除非安德伍德政府
But unless the Underwood administration
備好了上等大禮
is bearing top-tier gifts,
你敢讓前副總統幫忙
you've got a lot of fucking nerve
膽子還真是夠大
asking for favors from the former VP.
但話說回來  如果你能把事情處理好
On the other hand, if you make things right,
馬修斯會做好他該做的
Matthews will do his part.
你應該一向很同情那匹馬吧
Don't you always feel sorry for the horse?
會議室里是誰
Who's in the conference room?
-你是說娘子軍嗎  -什么
- You mean the lady brigade? - What?
就是國安局的法庭審計員
That's what they call the NSA forensic auditors.
我不知道她們今天要來
Yeah, I... I didn't know they were scheduled for today.
她們總這樣  就這么突然出現
That's their routine. They just show up.
國安局就這樣
Welcome to the NSA.
哥們
Hey, boss.
我可以吃嗎  總統先生
May I, Mr. President?
放著就是讓人吃的
Well, that's what they're there for.
我不會占用你太多時間
I won't take up much of your time.
我知道你下午很忙
I know you have a busy afternoon.
-我還是有點時間的  -我很好奇
- Well, I've got a little time. - I'm curious.
為什么委員會先給你打電話
Why do you think the committee decided to call you first?
因為是我要求的
Because I asked them to.
突然要參加
Well, this emergency
你召開的緊急州長會議  所以...
governors' conference of yours came up and, uh...
你肯定記得  我不怎么喜歡特區
I'm sure you recall, I don't much like DC,
所以我想著何不就一次都搞定呢
so I figured why not make it one-stop shopping?
是啊
Yes.
不過我們都知道  行使總統特權
But, of course, we both know that executive privilege
就可以替你省一樁事的
could've negated your having to appear at one of those shops.
吉姆
Jim?
我會幫你解決熔渣堆的事
I'm going to help you with your slag heap.
希望這樣一來我能指望上你
I hope that means that I can count on you.
當然了
Of course that's what it means.
我們是一個小型兄弟會的  都是前副總統
We're members of a tiny brotherhood, you and I, of ex-VPs.
如果加勒特·沃克去委員會作證
When, and if, Garrett Walker appears before this committee,
你覺得他會...
do you think he'll...
-背叛黨派嗎  -你是說背叛你嗎
- betray the party? - You mean you?
兩者是一回事
Well, that would be the same thing.
我不知道你接替了我副總統的職位
Now, I don't know what really happened
隨后又接替了加勒特總統的職位過程中
on your journey to replace me as vice president
究竟發生了什么
and then Garrett as president.
我只知道自己的直覺
I only know what my gut tells me.
但我愿意無視我的直覺
But I'm willing to say fuck my gut.
總而言之
Bottom line is
我能幫你搞定委員會  也能傷害你
I can help you with this committee or I can hurt you.
我可以說我一無所知
Now, I can say that I know nothing...
我認為加勒特·沃克是個有困擾的人
and that what I saw in Garrett Walker was a troubled man.
我可以只說這些
And I can leave it at that.
你覺得呢
What do you think?
我不能告訴你該怎么做  吉姆
Oh, I can't tell you what to do, Jim.
但我可以說  我們副總統不說兩家話
But I can say, as one ex-VP to another,
賓夕法尼亞州的清污工作
that this cleanup in Pennsylvania
價值三億美元和一萬個工作崗位
is gonna be worth about $300 million and 10,000 jobs.
一下午的辛勞能賺來這個不錯了
And that's not bad for an afternoon's work.
我喜歡這條新地毯
I like the new rug.
謝謝  其實都不是我弄的
Oh, thank you. I didn't have much to do with it.
是克萊爾布置的
It was really Claire's design.
很高興見到你  總統先生
Good to see you, Mr. President.
我也是
You, too.
斯坎倫州長
Governor Scanlon.
總統先生
Mr. President.
我一直掛記你
You've been on my mind.
我想跟你上司談談宣戰委員會的事
I wanna talk to your boss about the Declaration of War Committee.
如果
So...
你是想拿欠繳稅款的事來要挾他
if you're hoping to intimidate him because of the back taxes,
就別白費口舌了
you can save your breath.
事情都已經解決干凈了
His closet is back to being clean.
那你的事呢
What about yours?
-你就是個畜生  -我可沒看
- You're a pig. - Hey, I didn't watch it.
我只是傳話的
I'm just the messenger.
-盡管去生發帖人的氣吧  -生著呢
- Be mad at the dude who posted it. - I am.
有很多辦法能解決這個
There are ways to get rid of it.
這是份善意的禮物  讓你知道我是認真的
It's a goodwill gift. To let you know I'm serious.
我猜  早晚我會被傳召
Look, I'm guessing, sooner or later, I get called.
如果真這樣  我可以援引第五修正案的權利
And if that happens, I could plead the Fifth.
我也可以跟他們打一天太極
I could press-secretary them all day long.
但我希望還有別的選擇
But I'd like to have another option on the table.
我自己不能做公開證人
Yeah, I can't be a public witness myself...
但你要是能給我提供匿名權和豁免權...
but if you offer me anonymity and immunity...
我可以私下作證
I can testify privately.
告訴委員會"尸體"埋在哪了
Tell the committee where the bodies are buried, so to speak.
我確認一下  你是說
But, just to be clear, you're telling me
你有證據證明總統參與了犯罪活動
you have evidence the president engaged in criminal activity?
不是涉及總統的證據  不
Not evidence regarding the president, no.
我有很多關于他的幕僚長的料
I have a lot of information about his chief of staff.
道格·斯坦普
Doug Stamper.
跟你老板談談  告訴我結果
Talk to your boss. Let me know.
布莉姬特  說句題外話
Uh, Bridget, total non sequitur...
你的脖子真美
You have a very elegant neck.
格雷森先生嗎
Mr. Grayson?
我叫肖恩·杰弗瑞斯  《先驅報》的
Sean Jeffries. I'm with the Herald.
抱歉  沒辦法跟你握手
Sorry, I don't have a free hand.
你在報社待多久了
How long have you been with the paper?
13個月  時尚專欄的
Thirteen months. Style section.
難怪我不認識你
Oh, that would explain why I don't know you.
男人的領帶是心靈的窗戶
Man's tie is a window into his soul.
我們剛發了一篇相關文章
We just ran a piece on it.
是嗎  那從我的領帶能怎么解讀我
Oh, yeah? So, uh, what does my tie say about me?
你是個嘔心瀝血的公仆
It says you're a dedicated civil servant
有銀行賬戶可以證明
with the bank account to prove it.
總之  正好認出你了  順便打個招呼
Anyway, recognized you, just wanted to say hi.
當然  除非還能請你喝一杯
I mean, unless we can buy you a drink.
你認識卡姆·勞德嗎
You know, uh, Cam Lawder?
梅賽德斯奔馳的說客
Lobbyist for Mercedes-Benz?
他旁邊是金·菲爾舒克  國防部的
Next to him is, uh, Kim Feldshuk, works at the DOD.
那個是蘭迪·博福德
And that's Randy Beauford.
華盛頓死胖子們的私人教練
Personal trainer for fat Washington fucks.
今天下午我們走復古風
We're going old school this afternoon.
來吧  跟我們一起喝一杯
Come on, join us for a quick one.
"傳聲筒"
"Mouthpiece"?
我都不知道他干嗎要接受采訪
I don't know why he was talking to the press in the first place.
毫無疑問  湯姆選這么個詞真是不慎
An unfortunate choice of word for Tom, no doubt.
不過  熱度會很快過去的
But still, it'll play itself out.
但我想知道的是  你看出了什么
But what I want to know is, what do you see?
你為什么不喜歡耶茨
Why don't you like Yates?
湯姆是團隊里很重要的一部分
Uh, Tom is an important part of the team.
他的演講一直
His speeches have been--
聽著  他的責任遠不止如此
Oh, look. He has more responsibilities than that.
你知道的  所以你不高興
You know it. So that bothers you.
我只是不希望
I... just wouldn't want
有任何人進行對競選無用的
anyone to infer a personal investment on his part
個人投資
that isn't useful to the campaign.
我只是想表達
I suppose all I'm saying is that
我不會讓第一夫人
I won't let anything happen
或總統先生您出任何事
to the First Lady or you, Mr. President.
我很感激  莉安
I appreciate that, LeAnn.
我們完了  總統先生  原諒我爆粗口
We are fucked, Mr. President. Pardon my French.
我不關心你的粗口  你到底來干什么
I don't care about your French. Why am I even talking to you?
國安局派了審計員來
Well, the NSA has sent in auditors.
要是我不抹去我的檔案  掩蓋我的行蹤
If I don't erase my files, cover my tracks--
我們離選舉只有一周了  麥卡倫先生
We're a week away from the election, Mr. Macallan.
-掩蓋好你的行蹤  -好  這樣的話
- Cover your tracks. - Okay. In which case,
我得讓黑客們暫時
I need to let hackers temporarily
侵入東首都電信的一處轉接中心
invade a Capital East Telecom switching center.
什么意思
Meaning what?
中心承擔了大部分美國政府的網絡流量
Well, the center covers most of the US government cyber traffic.
但我如果登入  并在20分鐘內登出
But if I'm in and out in 20 minutes,
我想損害看上去也就是惡作劇級別的
I think the damage will look mischief-level.
連接故障之類的
Messed-up connections, that sort of thing.
-要是20分鐘沒出來呢  -不會的
- What if it takes you longer? - Uh, it won't,
因為再有十幾二十分鐘...
because another ten, 20 minutes and...
做吧
Do it.
好  我會在下午四點開始
All right. Well, I'll start it at 4:00 p.m.
我一弄完
Uh, as soon as I'm done,
就匿名發送一份修復代碼
I'll anonymously send out a fix to the problem.
-不  -先生
- No. - Sir?
莉安會通知你什么時候發送修復
LeAnn will contact you about when to send out the fix.
-你要等她的消息  -好  不過以防...
- You'll wait for her. - Okay, but just to be--
她會通知你的
She'll let you know.
我剛看了那篇海恩斯的文章
I just saw the Haines article.
我完全不知道湯姆怎么想的
I have no idea what Tom was thinking.
是啊
Yes.
太大意了
It was sloppy.
是啊  我會跟他談的
Agreed. I'll talk to him.
你還好嗎
Are you all right?
紐約怎么樣
How was New York?
我的活動進展順利
My events went well.
然后呢  你有什么沒告訴我的
And? What aren't you telling me?
我遇見肯·卡斯維爾了
I bumped into Ken Caswell.
-他還知道什么情況嗎  -不
- Does he know any more? - No, um...
-你為什么沒回他電話  -什么
- Why didn't you call him back? - What?
他財政部的事  監督立法
His Treasury business. The oversight legislation.
我明白你不在乎這個  無所謂
I understand you don't care about it. Fine.
但你不能無視遺患  你應該聽他說說
But you can't ignore loose ends like that. You owed him your ear.
我沒想到這事會那么傷感情
Well, I didn't realize it was gonna become so personal.
我可是美國總統
I am the President of the United States,
拜托  我有點忙啊
for Christ's sake. I'm a bit busy.
過往不是你一聲令下就能消失  弗蘭西斯
The past doesn't disappear on command, Francis.
哪怕是總統都不行
Not even for presidents.
他對你說什么了
What did he say to you?
肯有張大嘴巴
Ken's got a big mouth.
蒂姆的事我很遺憾  我很抱歉他不在了
I'm sorry about Tim. I'm sorry he's gone.
我知道你對他的感情
I know how you felt about him.
或者我能想象
Or, I can imagine.
聽我說
Listen to me.
你知道我這輩子只真正愛過你一個人
You know you're the only person I've ever truly loved.
你知道的吧
You know that, right?
你聽好
And listen.
有別的事就要發生了
Something else is about to happen.
歡迎回來
Welcome back.
信號不太好  還順利嗎
Reception is sketchy. Good trip?
我只是回來換衣服  馬上就得回去找弗蘭西斯
I just came back to get changed. I need to get back to Francis.
你生我氣了嗎
You mad at me?
你不應該那么說
You shouldn't have said that.
我知道  我知道我們需要小心
I know. I know we need to be careful.
我們可遠遠不止要小心
Careful is far too small a word for what we need to be.
好吧
Okay.
但是你就不累嗎
But don't you get tired of
整天不止要小心
being far bigger than careful all the time?
-我不知道是怎么回事  -我也不知道
- I don't know what's going on. - Me neither.
看來是網絡信號有干擾
Seems to be some kind of network disturbance.
我連不上服務器了
I lost connection on my server.
你知道我煩什么嗎  第一夫人這個角色
You know what I'm tired of? This role. First Lady.
因為感覺一直不對勁
'Cause it's never felt right.
再過八天  我就是副總統了
It's only eight more days to the vice presidency.
-那我的角色是什么  -什么
- What's my role? - What?
話說我到底是你什么人  或者你是我什么人
What am I to you, anyway? Or you, to me?
你是我女朋友嗎
I mean, are you my girlfriend?
等你當選了
And when you win...
那我是不是就成了  第一男友什么的
does that make me, like, First Boyfriend?
第一男寵
First Concubine?
那篇文章的事  我很抱歉
About that article... I'm sorry.
我討厭道歉
I hate apologies.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我當時看你了  看你目睹那一幕
I looked over at you. I watched you watching.
-什么時候  -對你有任何影響嗎
- When? - Did it even affect you?
斬首的畫面
The beheading?
問這個干什么
Why would you ask that?
我根本不知道你在想什么
I had no sense of what you were thinking.
完全不知道
None.
我在想什么  我什么都沒想
Of what I was thinking? I wasn't thinking.
我在想  "什么都別想"
I was thinking, "Don't think."
我再跟你說個別的事
And I'll tell you something else.
我可沒說過我喜歡整天小心
I never said I like being careful.
-可惡  -怎么了
- God damn it. - What's wrong?
衛星定位顯示我們還在白宮呢
The GPS thinks we're back at the White House.
你聯系上競選辦公室了嗎
Did you reach the campaign office?
正在打  總是沒信號
Trying. I can't get a signal.
等等  來信號了
Oh, wait. Here we go.
這班飛機我絕不能錯過
I can't miss this flight.
-正在接通  -太好了
- It's ringing. - Good.
-你看還需要多久  -又斷了
- How long do you think? - Now it stopped.
高速上堵車了  我在盡力了
There's a pile-up on the highway. I'm doing the best I can.
喂
Hello?
Hello!
塔妮婭  我拿你的手機試試
Tanya, let me try your phone.
我的手機也一樣
I'm having the same issues.
你能聯系上辦公室嗎
Can you get through to the office?
不行  州長  打不通
No, Governor, I can't.
加勒特是個好人
Garrett is a good man.
-他可靠嗎  -當然了  羅梅洛先生
- A trustworthy man? - Absolutely, Mr. Romero.
他是那種
And is he the kind of man
會蓄意參與競選資金欺詐的人嗎
who would knowingly participate in campaign finance fraud?
我不這么認為  不會
I wouldn't say that, exactly. No.
你和安德伍德總統熟悉嗎  先生
How well do you know President Underwood, sir?
我認識總統4年了
I've known the president four years.
是弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
Isn't it a fact that it was Francis Underwood
而不是沃克總統最先建議你辭職的吧
and not President Walker who first suggested you should resign?
據我回憶  不是的
To the best of my recollection, no.
而且你身為總統競選搭檔收到的競選經費
And isn't it true that the source of campaign funds you received
追根溯源  和一起從密蘇里
as the president's running mate was connected to
波及到中國的賄賂案件有聯系吧
a pay-for-play scheme that reached all the way from Missouri to China?
據我所知  不是的
To the best of my knowledge, no.
你們沒通過雷蒙德·塔斯克的公司
Did you receive any campaign donations
克雷頓-維斯特收到任何競選捐助嗎
through Raymond Tusk's firm, Clayton West?
據我回憶  沒有
Not to the best of my recollection.
你的回憶和了解
Do you think your recollection
會隨著時間推移而變化嗎
or knowledge will improve as the day goes on?
什么
Excuse me?
貝絲
Beth.
你要向我保證  無論有什么需要
I want you to promise me that you'll call me
都會打給我
anytime you need anything.
你是蒂姆的一生摯愛
You were the love of Tim's life, you know that.
我還是...
Well, I should probably...
對  你也是
Yes. You, too.
再見
Goodbye.
謝謝你  菲利克斯
Thank you, Felix.
需要我幫你點起來嗎  總統先生
Uh, would you like me to prepare it for you, sir?
不用了  謝謝你
No, I'll be fine. Thank you.
首先要問的問題是  進氣口打開了嗎
The first question to ask yourself... "Is the damper open?"
一定不要讓自己被煙霧包圍
Never allow yourself to be overcome with smoke.
火勢要起來  必須要通氣  所以火爐才有格柵
Conflagration relies on airflow. That's what the grate is for.
底下的灰一英寸就夠了
Now, I like a one-inch base of ash.
確實有用  但是
It's helpful, but of course
他們清理得太頻繁了
they clean up around here too soon to do that.
至于怎么擺放木材
Now, as for the architecture of the logs,
我建議倒置擺放
I prefer the upside-down method.
大塊木材放在底下
Largest logs right along the base.
上面是中塊的
Then medium-size logs after that.
小塊的
Small logs.
最后  是引火木
And then finally, kindling...
和火絨
and tinder.
當然  家鄉有枯了的棕櫚葉  那個最理想
Now, of course, back home, dead palmetto fronds are ideal.
不過在華盛頓
But, of course, here in Washington,
手邊有什么垃圾都得拿來用
we have to use whatever garbage we find lying around.
但如果利用不好手邊...
But then, if a man cannot use what's right in...
該死  蒂姆
God damn it, Tim.
如果你不夠聰明
If a man is not smart enough
利用不好手邊的資源
to be able to use whatever is in front of him
辦不成事
and still make it work...
那就是
well, then...
你自己無能了
that's just a failure of the imagination.
...就在這兒  我還想
...right here. And I'm thinking...
"等等  要告訴他嗎"
"Wait, do I tell him? Do--"
我得接
Uh, I gotta take this.
你不能私下作證
Your testimony can't be private.
-真遺憾  -就告訴你一下
- I'm sorry to hear that. - Just wanted to let you know.
"快閃血警告"是什么
What's a "flash blood warning"?
大家的手機上都有
It's coming up on everybody's phones.
謝謝你們的酒
Thanks for the drinks.
湯姆  停下  我得回去了
Tom, stop. No. I... I have to get back.
別這樣
Come on.
不行
No.
湯姆
Tom!
最后  劃一下火柴
And, finally, you strike your match...
點燃引火木
you ignite your kindling...
然后吹氣
and then you blow.
開始了  先生
It's happening, sir.
請市民們注意
Citizens should be advised,
目前華盛頓特區的網絡
a wave of disruptions is currently affecting
和手機信號正受到干擾
Internet and cellular service in the DC area.
交通及出行可能受影響
Expect traffic and travel delays
官方仍在努力
as authorities are still trying
確定問題的影響范圍
to determine the scope of the problem.
-能趕上飛機嗎  -不知道
- Are we gonna make this flight? - I don't know.
有消息推測
Unconfirmed reports speculate
干擾可能是一起網絡攻擊
the disruptions may be connected to a cyber-attack
并與哈里發國有聯系
with possible ties to ICO.
-天哪  -怎么了
- My God. - What?
也許他們是對的
Maybe they were right.
也許我們該同意警衛隊的提議
Maybe we should have said yes to the offer of those troops.
國民警衛隊的巡邏
National Guard on patrol
會讓我們在選舉前顯得軟弱  不行
makes us look weak right before an election. Forget it.
-但州長  -我已經決定了  塔妮婭
- But, Governor-- - I made my decision, Tanya.
還不行
Not yet.
各運營商老板正在接入  先生
They're patching through the heads of all the carriers, sir.
先生們女士們  能聽到嗎
Gentlemen and ladies, can you hear me?
能  總統先生
Yes, Mr. President.
好  告訴我這究竟是怎么回事
Good. Then tell me how in God's name this has happened.
還不清楚  先生  我們還在檢修故障
Uh, we don't know yet, sir. We're still working on the problem.
我們正在盡可能多地聯系...
We're reaching out to as many people as we--
我們掉線了嗎
Did we just lose them?
開什么玩笑
Is this a joke?
俄亥俄州州長用付費電話打來的
The Ohio governor is calling from a payphone.
我是總統
This is the president.
總統先生  我改主意了
Mr. President, I've changed my mind.
如果您的提議還有效
If the offer's still open,
我想接受增派警衛隊到俄亥俄州來
I'd like to accept additional troops for the state of Ohio.
只要你開口  羅杰  都隨你
Just say the word, Roger. Whatever you need.
美國同胞們  事情是這樣的
My fellow Americans, the facts are these.
哥倫比亞特區及周邊地區
The greater District of Columbia area and the immediate region beyond
正在遭受疑似是哈里發國所為的網絡攻擊
have undergone what we suspect is an ICO-sponsored cyber-attack.
這次攻擊針對的是
The attack was aimed at
特區的主要電信交換中心
the district's main telecom switching center.
目前不僅信號斷斷續續
In addition to intermittent outages,
還引發了大規模的破壞
a considerable amount of havoc has been wreaked.
交通信號燈失靈
Traffic lights have been disabled.
一區列車脫軌
One area train has been derailed.
下水道維護系統遭到破壞
The system that maintains our sewers has been tampered with.
罪犯的目標是政府
The perpetrators were targeting the government
雖然他們的最終目的
and their ultimate purpose, though foiled,
是干擾大西洋中部的交通網絡  但遭挫敗
was to disrupt all mid-Atlantic transportation networks.
這類事件說明了
Events like these underscore
通過我向國會提交的宣戰請求
the urgency of my request to Congress
是多么緊急
for a declaration of war.
今晚  我想
Tonight, I can only suspect
國會將會追悔莫及
Congress will spend a dark night of the soul,
然后他們會反思自己的失職  并采取行動
after which they will reconsider their paralysis and choose to act.
東首都電信告訴我
Capital East Telecom has informed me
他們正在盡快修復網絡
that it's repairing the network as fast as possible,
但需要至少幾天時間才能完全恢復
but that it will take at least a couple more days to be fully restored.
很遺憾但又不可否認的是
It is an unfortunate but undeniable fact
我們會繼續遭到攻擊
that we will continue to experience attacks
除非哈里發國和類似恐怖組織
until ICO and other terrorist groups like it
被快速一舉消滅
are eliminated swiftly and completely.
謝謝  天佑國民
Thank you. May God bless you.
天佑美利堅合眾國
And may God bless the United States of America.
下線了嗎
We off?
-晚上好  泰德  -你好  漢娜
- Good evening, Ted. - Hi, Hannah.
我看了你的采訪
I saw your interview.
我希望
I'd appreciate it
你別提起我戰斗記錄的細節
if you didn't bring up the details of my combat record.
你那天很英勇  你應該利用起來  威爾
You were a hero that day. You should use it, Will.
州長  恐怖分子正在襲擊
Governor, aren't you worried about
難道你帶孩子們出門不會擔心嗎
bringing your kids out in the middle of a terrorist attack?
讓孩子在家里更可怕
It'd be scarier to keep the kids at home.
街頭很安全  生活得繼續
The streets are safe. Life goes on.
在開玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
你有什么想法  州長
What's on your mind, Governor?
我有什么想法  你們都看到了
What's on my mind? I mean, you see what's going on here.
都是他干的  一個從沒服過役的人
This is all him. It's a man who's never served.
哪怕戰爭咬上他的屁股
Wouldn't know what a real war was
他都認不出來
if it jumped up and bit him in the ass.
還要宣戰
I mean, a declaration of war?
他在危及美國人的生命
He's putting American lives in danger.
-戰爭不是兒戲  -喝一杯嗎
- War is real! - Nightcap?
-你不能亂來  -好啊
- You don't screw around with it. - Why not?
亂來就會變成這樣
This is what happens.
當你濫用"戰爭"這個詞  事情就會變成這樣
This is what happens when you throw around a word like "War."
全都亂作一團
All hell breaks loose.
壓制投票的問題是近些年美國兩黨分歧較大  斗爭激烈的一個政治議題
這個問題的核心是  共和黨主張為了防止選舉舞弊
應該在投票時要求選民出示有效的身份證件  但是民主黨認為
由于民主黨選民大多生活窘困  辦理駕照或身份證件很困難
所以要求出示身份證件  實際上就是要阻止底層選民投票
而共和黨反過來指控民主黨這種立場是鼓勵有利于自己的非法移民投票
這一問題在美國多地引發了多起高調的訴訟
一般是一些共和黨占多數的州議會和政府出臺相關法律
要求投票時出示證件  然后支持民主黨的民權組織提起訴訟
稱這種法律違憲  目前美國有多個州的選民證件法面臨法律挑戰
其它壓制投票的方法還有減少投票點  縮短提前投票時間等